Wil kicked me out of his D&D game.
威尔把我踢出了他的《龙与地下城》游戏局
You were in Wil's D&D game?
你参加了威尔的《龙与地下城》游戏吗
- With William Shatner? - And you didn't tell us?
-和威廉·夏特纳一起  -你居然没告诉我们
I'm sorry, Wil made me promise not to.
对不起  威尔让我发誓不说出去
I thought we were friends.
我以为我们是朋友
Oh, come on, you guys would do the same thing.
得了  你们也会这样做的
No, we wouldn't! I told you when I was in spin class with Scarlett Johansson.
不  我们不会  我在动感单车课上  碰到斯嘉丽·约翰逊  我就告诉你了
It didn't even turn out to be Scarlett Johansson.
结果根本不是斯嘉丽·约翰逊
Well, that's her fault, not mine!
那是她的错  不关我事
It doesn't matter  because Penny blabbed about it and now I'm out.
根本不重要了  因为佩妮到处大嘴巴  现在我出局了
So there's an open seat.
所以说空出来一个位置